Hi.
Good morning, tiger.
I'm making you
a nice big breakfast
so you can keep up
your strength for tonight.
You're going to get me
good and pregnant.
I've got nowhere to go
this morning.
I'm unemployed.
I don't know what I'm going
to do with my life.
Well, I just lost my erection.
No, I mean, what
am I supposed to
do with myself?
You're supposed to find
your passion in life.
You can be whatever
you want to be now.
It's exciting.
Yeah, it's also overwhelming.
I mean, I don't know
where to start.
Hey, wait a second.
I can help you with this.
You just need
to be organized.
We can make a list
of your qualifications
and categorize jobs
by industry.
There could be folders
and files...
Hey, this is where
your hyper-organized
pain-in-the-ass
stuff pays off.
I know!
My erection is back.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Thank you.
Joey, could I have
a sip of your coffee
and a bite
of your muffin?
Okay.
Thank you.
Uh, Pheebs, have you ever been
bitten by a hungry Italian?
I'm sorry.
It's just, I'm a little
short on cash.
If you want, I could
loan you some money.
Oh, no, no, no.
I learned never borrow
money from friends.
No, that's why
Richard Dreyfuss and I
don't speak anymore.
Ooh, hey, how about this?
Want to be an extra on my show?
You could do that?
Yeah, yeah.
The pay is pretty good
and you could do it
for as long as you need.
Oh, my God,
I'm going to be on TV.
Okay, now, I got to tell you
being on TV isn't as glamorous
and exciting as you think.
Oh, really?
No, it is awesome.
Hey, guys.
Hey.
Oh, wow.
Hey, why are you
all dressed up?
Rachel and I are bringing
Emma to Ralph Lauren today
to introduce her
to everyone.
Doesn't she look cute?
She sure does.
Why does she have a pink bow
taped to her head?
Well, because if one more person
says "What a cute little boy"
I'm going to whip them
with a car antenna.
I think she's going to be
the hit of the office, huh?
She's going to be hotter
than peasant blouses
and A-line skirts.
Can I get a blue bow?
Okay, I have looked through
a bunch of career guides
photocopied and highlighted
key passages
and put them into
alphabetical folders
so you can make
an informed decision.
How long was I
in there?
Okay, let's start with the As.
Advertising.
Wait.
That's a great idea.
Well, don't you want
to look through the rest?
I don't think I have
to hear the rest.
Advertising makes
perfect sense.
Sorry you had to waste
all this time, though.
You call eight hours alone
with my label maker wasted time?
Ooh, now I'll get to use
my shredder.
I mean, I could
write slogans.
How hard could
it be, right?
Cheese.
It's milk... that you chew.
Crackers.
Because your cheese
needs a buddy.
A grape.
Because who can get a watermelon
in your mouth?
I got one.
Socks. Because your family's
feet deserve the best.
Honey, leave it to the pros.
I actually know someone
in advertising.
I grew up with this guy
who is a vice president
at a big agency.
Maybe I can get him
to meet you.
Give me the phone.
The phone.
Bringing you closer to
people who have phones.
Marriage.
It's not for everybody.
Well, that went well.
Almost everybody knew
that she was a girl.
Yeah, after you punched
that one guy who got it
wrong, word spread.
All right, well, I'm just
going to go in my office
and pick up some stuff.
Who the hell are you?
I'm the hell person
whose office this is.
Good one, Rach.
I'm Gavin Mitchell, the person
who's taken over your job.
Excuse me?
Oh, your baby's
so cute.
Why would you put
a pink bow on a boy?
Hey, Joey, look at me.
I'm a nurse.
Yes, you are.
Think it might be time
for my sponge bath.
Sorry, I'm just so used
to hitting on the extras.
So are you excited
about your scene?
Yeah, but I'm a little
shaky and nervous.
Oh, relax, don't be.
You'll be fine.
They'll probably just make you
stand in the background.
Okay, okay, okay, you.
Here, come here.
You're going to take this tray,
stand on this yellow mark.
You're going to move
on "action."
You're going to walk over
to the operating table
stop on that blue mark,
put the tray down.
Don't walk too fast.
But don't dawdle.
Okay, now, what?
And... action!
( rattling )
Cut! Cut!
I'm sorry,
I'm sorry.
I'm just a
little nervous.
Yeah, well, don't be.
Okay, that helps.
And... action!
( rattling )
( clanging )
Cut!
Hey, don't worry
about it, Pheebs.
Usually takes me
three takes, too.
All right, eight.
And...
Action!
( rattling )
( clanging )
So, do you have
any other questions
about advertising?
No, no.
But let me show you
what I can do.
Bagels and doughnuts.
Round food for every mood.
Monica warned me
you might do that.
I actually think
we might have something
for you at the agency.
Really?
That's great.
It's an unpaid internship.
That's funny.
When you said "unpaid"
it sounded like
you said "unpaid."
Come on, now,
Monica has a good job.
And it's not like
you have a family to support.
Well, actually, we're trying.
And I don't think Monica's
going to want to postpone it.
We're supposed
to have sex tonight.
Actually, she's probably
at home naked right now.
I tend to keep talking
until somebody stops me.
You can just picture her
on the bed right now...
Stop!
Okay.
Wait a minute.
What do you mean
you're taking over my job?
Well, while you were
on your baby vacation
I was doing your job.
A vacation?
My idea of a vacation
does not involve
something sucking on my nipples
until they are raw.
Clearly you've never been
to Sandals Paradise Island.
Well, don't get
too comfortable there
because I'm back in two weeks.
And I want everything back
to the way it was.
I can't say that I care too much
for the way that you've
rearranged my office.
I can't say I care too much
for that smell
you've brought in with you.
Excuse me?
Uh, Rach...
we have a Code Brown situation.
Well, could you please, please
take care of it for me?
All right, but you have
to do one some time.
Let me just
get this straight.
So I go have a baby and they
send some guy in to do my job?
Well, there was talk of shutting
down Ralph Lauren altogether.
You're very cheeky for a temp.
I'm not a temp.
I was transferred here
from another department.
Oh, yeah, and what
department was that
the jerk department?
Oh, they didn't tell me
about your quick wit.
Ah, well,
did they mention
that I'm rubber
and you're glue?
Gavin, Ralph loved your ideas.
Oh, hi, Mr. Zelner.
Ah, Rachel.
I see you've met Gavin.
You know, I must say
when you left us
we weren't sure what
we were going to do.
But then,
Gavin to the rescue.
Super Gavin.
Well, that's great,
that's great.
So now, Super Gavin,
when I come back
where do you plan on
flying off to?
Well, that's
up to Mr. Zelner.
I'm sure he'll make
the right decision.
( sotto ):
Oh, wow,
Super Ass Kissing Power.
Incidentally,
when are you coming back?
Uh, today.
You said two weeks.
No, I said today.
See, for a super hero,
not so much with the listening.
Hey. So what'd he say?
Uh...
well, he can be a little
rough around the edges.
So I'm going to replace
a word he used a lot
with the word "puppy."
Okay?
So he said,
"If your puppy friend
"doesn't get her
puppy act together
I am going to fire
her mother puppy ass."
I'm sorry.
I can't do this.
I'm just not an actor.
That's right, you're not.
You're a nurse.
You're Nurse With Tray.
Joey...
No, no, Nurse With Tray
doesn't know Joey.
She doesn't have time
for friends.
She gets in
that operating room
and she carries that tray
to the doctor
because if she doesn't,
people die.
Who dies?
Man With Eye Patch.
Now you get in there
and you do your job.
Yes, doctor.
Okay.
( claps ):
Let's try this
one more time.
Hang in there,
Man With Eye Patch
your tray is coming.
And... action.
Yes! I did it! I nailed it!
Whoo!
What's next?
The rest of the scene.
Okay, from the top, people.
Listen, sudden
change in plans.
My maternity leave
just ended.
They told me that
if I didn't come
back today
they were going
to fire me.
What the...?
That's illegal.
I'm going to have
the Labor Department
down here so fast,
they won't even...
All right, calm down, Norma Rae.
They didn't actually
say that.
I'm just afraid
if I don't come
back right now
this guy's going
to try to squeeze me out.
But what about Emma?
We don't have a nanny.
I know.
You know what--
we're just going
to have to figure out
a plan tonight.
Can you please just
take care of her for today?
Absolutely.
Just give me your breasts
and we'll be on our way.
Come on, I don't know
what else to do.
Fine. Fine.
We'll have fun, won't we?
Yes, we will...
( kissing sound )
Ross...
Huh?
You're pretty.
Whatever I decide to do
I'm going to be starting
an new career from scratch.
It's going to be a while
before I make a living at it.
Maybe now is not
the right time
to be starting
a family.
So you have
to tell Monica
you don't want to have
a baby right now?
Yeah.
Good-bye.
Okay, it's baby time.
Pants off, Bing.
Didn't see you there, Geller.
Yeah, Ross is here, so...
Yeah, uh-huh, yeah.
And I was really hoping that
maybe I could hang out.
Hmm.
You know, what do you
feel like doing?
Well, we're going
to have sex.
I don't feel like
having sex.
Uh, maybe, uh, I don't know
maybe we can watch
a movie or something.
Let me put it this way--
we're having sex
whether you're here or not.
Pants off, Bing.
All right, now
that I'm back
why don't you just
fill me in on
what you've been up to.
Well, I changed your
screen saver
from that picture
of NSYNC.
Hey, they were popular
when I left.
But mostly I've just
been working on
this big presentation
for tomorrow.
Well, I should be
involved in that
so why don't you get
me up to speed?
That's going to take weeks.
Why don't you let me
take care of the presentation?
Oh, no, no, no.
I see what you're
doing here, all right?
Listen, this is
my job, buddy.
Okay, I've had it
for five years
and I know how it works.
So why don't you
just catch me up.
Fine.
Oh, God.
You totally messed with
the back support on my chair.
How do you fix this?
Hey, you've been here five
years, you figure it out.
Fine, I will.
All right, fill me in.
Hey.
Do you have a blue tie
that would go with this?
Emma spit up on mine.
Yeah, but you have
to give it
back if I get a job.
Of course, by that time
in the future
ties will be obsolete
and we'll be wearing
silver jumpsuits.
Hey, good morning, lover.
I've got to say
after last night,
I'm a little weak
in the knees.
Here's an idea:
you walk into a room,
take a quick scan.
Sorry.
But I kind of have
this feeling
that we may have
made a baby last night.
Oh, God, I have
to tell you something.
You're not pregnant.
What are you talking about?
Well, that thing
that I have to do
to make a baby...
I faked it.
What?!
You faked it?!
You know what?
I don't need a tie.
It's... it's better open collar,
you know.
It's... more casual.
Joey.
Listen, I can't
do this.
It doesn't make any sense.
Yesterday I was a nurse
and today I'm a waitress
in a cafe?
Oh, well, sometimes we use the
same extras for different parts.
It's okay.
Well, it's not okay
because I gave a very memorable
performance as the nurse.
And now,
suddenly I'm the waitress?
That's going to confuse
my fans.
Um, uh...
Maybe... you are a nurse
but you moonlight as a waitress.
Oh.
Uh-huh.
Because I'm a single mother
supporting my two children.
Nice.
Yeah.
Wait a minute.
Dr. Drake Ramoray
and I work at the same hospital.
Wouldn't I come over
to say hi to him?
No, no.
See, you and Drake are
having a fight.
About what?
He slept with you
and then never called you.
And I just wanted a new daddy
for Davey and Becky.
Okay, okay, from the top.
And... action.
So, I'm surprised you agreed
to have lunch with me.
I'm surprised, too,
but yet here I am.
Cut! Cut!
What... what are
you doing?!
Yeah, well, I'm
very angry at him
because he slept with me
and never called me back.
Me, too.
Oh, calm down.
She means on the show.
We need some new extras
around here.
Wow, you're here
already.
Yes. Emma and I came in
a little early
to do research
on the presentation.
Actually, I made a few changes
but I think I'm caught up
on everything.
So ask me anything.
How do you fix the chair?
Except that!
Oh, hello
Mr. Zelner.
We are all ready for our
presentation this afternoon.
Good, because
it's in ten minutes.
RACHEL:
What?
I can't do that.
I have the baby
and Ross is not going
to pick her up for another hour.
Well, then Gavin can
give the presentation, okay?
We have to do it now.
Ralph needs to leave
early today.
He's going helicopter shopping.
All right, well, there you go,
you win.
You win. You get to do
the presentation.
You'll knock 'em dead.
No one will ever remember
that I worked here.
And then Ralph will buy
his helicopter
and Super Gavin will just fly
right alongside of him.
You can do the presentation.
No, I can't.
I have a baby.
I'll watch her.
Why would you do that?
Because you worked
really hard
and it's your job
and you're a little crazy.
( voice breaking ):
That's really nice.
I should tell you
that crying women
make me very uncomfortable.
Well, you're not going
to like what's coming.
( sobbing )
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Thank you.
I'm really fine.
Don't worry,
I'm great with children.
Gavin Mitchell.
Pleased to meet you.
Please don't
fire my friend.
Just let me talk to her.
Okay, okay, but this
is her last chance.
Thank you,
thank you.
How about I do
something for you?
Tomorrow I'll bring
you hat-- cover up the bald.
Hey, listen, Pheebs,
I was just talking
to the director
and he was thinking
maybe this time
you don't hit Drake--
you just wait on the tables.
I can't do that.
I'm an actor.
I have a process.
You're a masseuse.
You have a table
with a hole in it.
Wait a minute,
I see what's happening here.
You're threatened.
What?
Yeah, I'm so good
in the scene
that I'm stealing focus
from you.
Well, rise
to the challenge, Tribbiani
'cause I just raised the bar.
Come join me up here.
( chuckling )
Yeah, you can fire her
but I would call security.
She won't go easy.
You faked it?
You couldn't have faked it.
Oh, yes, you can.
You just make the faces
and the noises.
Guys can fake it?
Unbelievable.
The one thing that's ours.
Besides, why would you fake it
when we're trying
to have a baby?
Well, that's
actually why.
Look, I'm starting
a whole new career now.
And I'm not saying
I don't want to have a baby.
I'm just saying, maybe
we could wait a little while.
Like... like a month?
Or a year?
Really? You want to wait a year?
Well, it could be
less than a year.
I mean, you've
heard my stuff.
Pants...
like shorts, but longer.
It'll probably be
more than a year.
Wow, I... really want
to have a baby.
Yeah, me, too.
Look, I'll just get
my old job back.
No, I want you
to have a job
that you love.
Not statistical analysis
and data reconfiguration.
I quit and you learn
what I do?
I just... I think
there's never going to be
a right time to have a baby.
I mean, now you're unemployed
and in a little while,
you'll find a new job
that'll keep you really busy.
There's always going to be
a reason not to do this
but once the baby comes
we'll forget about
all those reasons.
I guess.
I mean, it's always
going to be scary
when we have a baby.
It's going to be really scary.
But I mean, God,
when we have a baby
there's going to be so much
that we're not able to control.
The apartment's going
to be a mess.
I won't have time to clean it.
What if the baby gets
into the ribbon drawer?
Messes up all the ribbons?
What if there's no room
for a ribbon drawer
because the baby's stuff
takes up all the space?
Where will all the ribbons go?!
Should we go make a baby right
now before you change your mind?
Yes, please.
Oh, and I promise
I will not fake it this time.
I wish I could say the same.
I'm a little shook up.
I know you botched
that operation on purpose.
I can't prove it yet
but when I do, you'll be
going to jail for murder.
I don't care
if you are my brother.
I'm not your brother.
What about my
children, Drake, huh?
No! No!
No!
God!
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org